## **MOHIT GARG**

## Software & Network Engineer

Resourceful Software & Network Engineer with hands-on experience in software development and frameworks. Well-versed in software development methodologies. Talented at object-oriented design, functional programming paradigms and various development languages. Demonstrated excellent skills in HTML, JavaScript and Python. True team player with strengths in adaptability and accuracy.

## **Work History**

## 2020-09 -2021-07

## **Experience Technical Support Analyst**

Teleperformance, Toronto

- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems
- Managed over 60 customers calls per day resulting in increasing productivity of company.
- Successfully maintained clean, valid driver's license and access to reliable transportation
- Maintained energy and enthusiasm in fast-paced environment
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions

## 2018-02 -2020-06

## **Network Support Technician/Analyst**

Link-On Communications, Etobicoke

- Designed and evaluated WAN and LAN connectivity technologies
- Traveled to remote client locations to install nodes and implement client software rollouts
- Troubleshot hardware and software to determine and rectify network problems
- Installed cabling, wireless routers and telephone systems for data communications networks
- Maintained network connectivity of workstations, servers and network devices

## Contact

#### **Address**

Brampton, Ontario, L6P3S8

#### Phone

6475514760

#### E-mail

kishulehra@gmail.com

## **Skills**

Desktop Hardware and Software installation



Technical issues analysis



API design knowledge



Technical Support



Web & Network Security



Architectural pattern development



HTML, JAVA, CSS, React, C#, .NET Programming



## **Education**

# 2015-09 - Associate of Applied Science: Computer Software and Network Technician

Sheridan College - Brampton, ON High Honors, GPA: 3.91/4

## Certifications

2022-04 AWS Certified Solutions Architect

2022-03 AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner